BOJANA ZIVKOVIC

Address: 55 Sunrise Avenue, Murrays Bay, Auckland 0630

Mobile: +64 22 423 0268 Email: bojana.zivkovic@gmail.com

SUMMARY

With a Diploma in Software Engineering and Information Technologies, I have extensive exposure to different systems and technologies. In particular, I know Windows and Linux systems, DNS, Internet protocols, hosting, and also experience using programming languages and various frameworks for creating web applications. I have experience in developing and managing MySQL and SQL databases, as well as in deploying, maintain and administering applications on Linux and Windows.

At this moment, as a Web Developer, I am responsible for finding the most suitable web solutions and their implementations for various New Zealand clients, mostly with WordPress or custom PHP.

TOOLS AND SKILLS

- PHP 5.x / PHP 7.4
- MySQL, MS SQL databases
- SQL Server
- HTML, CSS, XML, Bootstrap, DataTables
- JavaScript, JSON, Ajax, jQuery
- Windows 7, Windows 10
- Linux environments
- LAMP, Shell scripting

- GIT, SVN
- Apache
- WordPress, Joomla, Drupal
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Office 365
- Excel VBA and macros for document automation
- Sharepoint

- Experience with SimPRO Operations Management Software
- Experience with MYOB AccountRight
- Experience with Trello Boards
- Experience with Jira

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer (Freelancer)

Digital Fix Ltd Auckland, New Zealand

August 2020 - present

[Web Application Development Company.]

- Website development (WordPress, PHP, MySQL, SQL, HTML, CSS)
- Website deployment and publishing
- Maintenance and updating of existing WordPress sites

Domain Name Registration and Data Analysis Coordinator

Serbian National Internet Domain Registry (RNIDS),

October 2017 - Nov 2019

ordinator Belgrade, Serbia (www.rnids.rs)

[The Serbian National Internet Domain Registry Foundation manages the registry of the national internet domain names .RS and .SRB and the Internet infrastructure of special importance for the functioning of the Internet in Serbia.]

- 1st and 2nd level Support for registrars in all aspects (administrative and technical)
- Domain name data analysis and writing report
- Development, deployment and maintenance of the RNIDS stats data platform
- Development and deployment of the application for financial management for RNIDS co-owners
- Writing scripts for searching DNS zone files
- Development of web service to connect SMS Gateway with PRTG Network monitor application
- Deployment and customization of Zonemaster.rs platform and Implementation of IDN converter
- Daily system monitoring and reviewing application logs
- Linux application deployment and maintenance
- Testing applications and EPP protocol

Developer

Pension and Disability Insurance Fund of the Republic of Serbia, Directorate, Belgrade, Serbia (www.pio.rs)

May 2015 - June 2017

[The Disability and Pension Fund of the Republic of Serbia has been established according to the Law on Pension and Disability Insurance, to execute rights from pension and disability insurance and provide funds to achieve these *rights*.]

- Maintenance of the www.pio.rs website (Joomla) and implementation of new functionality
- Development and maintenance of the intranet site (PHP, MySQL, jQuery)
- Creating reports with Jasper Reports and maintaining Jasper Server
- Development of various other smaller intranet applications and services with PHP

Web Developer

Iron Trust doo, Belgrade, Serbia

July 2014 - January 2015

[Iron Trust is the pioneer in records and information management in Cyprus, offering efficient, cost-effective and secure solutions to hundreds of businesses and organizations, from every industry sector.]

- Maintenance of company website in WordPress (iron-trust.rs and iron-trust.com)
- Development of corporate identity
- In charge of the Information Security Management System of organizations (ISMS) ISO 27001: 2013
- Maintenance of social network accounts

Web Operator

Halo oglasi doo, Belgrade, Serbia

June 2007 - November 2011

[The most powerful advertisement on the market and the website www.halooglasi.com, which records over 1.7 million unique visitors per month, are the largest stock market in Serbia.]

- Editing and correction of internet and SMS online web ads

Web Developer

Core Impulse doo, Belgrade, Serbia

October 2005 - June 2006

[Web Application Development Company]

- Maintenance and updating web sites (HVB bank, EFG bank, FIC - Foreign Investors Council, PwC)

EDUCATION

ICT College of Vocational Studies, University of Belgrade, Belgrade

2015 - 2016

Professional title: Specialist vocational engineer of electrical and computer engineering (Specialist)

Module:Software Engineering

Faculty of Computer Science, University Union, Belgrade

2009 - 2013

Professional title: Vocational engineer of electrical and computer engineering

Module:InformationTechnologies

REFERENCES

Available upon request